Guide to the Henry Taube Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2007-148
  - Halpern Symposium - 10/96 Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Hong Kong Perspectives Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Honolulu, 1995, Vania Fe(CN)6 + RuA5(H2O) Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Ion Clusters - Pullman Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Ion Clusters, Ventura 1997 Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Transparencies - Japan Trip 9/00 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Metal Ions in Biological General (Transparencies) (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Mixed Valence - Miscellaneous (Transparencies) (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Mixed valence Molecules '91 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Molecular Hysterisis Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Mixed Valence (Current) Transparencies - Slides Misc. (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - New Chemistry of hex … Ion Pairs … Australian Lecture Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - New Os chemistry - Ware and Droege (Transparencies) (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - NMR, 50 Years at Stanford Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Nobel (slides) (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Nobel (early) (transparencies) (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Nobel Transparencies (later) (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Nobel - Miscellaneous Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - 0 Atom Transfer (Slides) (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Organometal Catalysis - Barcelona (Transparencies) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Os-Chem Lund Transparencies (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Os Chemistry (Harman) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Os (II) - Miscellaneous (Transparencies) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Reactions of O2 (Transparencies) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Reactivity Inorganic Conf. Osaka, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Oxidation Reduction Reactions (unlabeled folder) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Short of Long Range Electron Transfer ACS April '92 Transparencies (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Tahoe, June '86 - Introductory Material (Transparencies) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Taube Symposium Transparencies (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Henry Taube - Wayne Wilmarth Seminar January 1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Toronto - New Transparencies (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Ventura 1999 Transparencies (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Recommendations A (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Recommendations B (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Recommendations C (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Recommendations D (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Recommendations E (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Recommendations F (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Recommendations G (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Recommendations H-I (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Recommendations J (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Recommendations K (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Recommendations L (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Recommendations M (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Recommendations Mc (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Recommendations N (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Recommendations O (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Recommendations P-Q (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Recommendatioons R (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Recommendations S (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Recommendations T (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Recommendations W (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Recommendations U-V (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Recommendations XYZ (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Henry Taube - Allied Chemical Award 1979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Henry Taube - Australian Academy of Science Awards (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Brazilian Chem. Soc. Award - HT (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Awards - C&E News Top 75 Contributors (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Henry Taube - Brazailian Academy of Sciences Awards (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Honorary Fellowship, the Royal Society of Canada, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Chemical Society of Japan (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Henry Taube - Engineering Academy of Japan Awards (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Henry Taube - Gibbs Award 1971 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Hungarian Academy of Sciences (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Henry Taube - Lajos Kossuth University of Debrecen (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Henry Taube - Misc. honors and awards (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Monsanto Award - 1980 - Taube, H. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Henry Taube - Nichols Award - 1971 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Henry Taube - National Medal of Science Award - 1977 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Royal Society (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Henry Taube - Museum of Science and Ind. Nobel Awards dinner - Chicago, ILL, Apr.'84 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Henry Taube - Nobel Prize 1983 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Ordre Souverain Militaire de Saint-Jean de Jerusalem - Knight Grand Cross of Malta (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Pauling Award April 1982 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Polytechninc Commencement May 1984 Honorary Doctor of Science Degree (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Priestly Medal (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Henry Taube - T. W. Richards Medal (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Royal Society of Chemistry (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Henry Taube - Welch FDN Prize 1983 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Henry Taube -personal items sent to 3D International in re Welch Prize (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Henry Taube - Welch congratulations letters (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Henry Taube - Marguerite Blake Wilbur Professor of Chemistry (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Australia (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Barcelona (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Camberra Lecture, 2/96 - background (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - China trip - H. Taube 1984 corres. Re possible (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - China - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Baker, J. T. lecture (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Act talk 1989 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Basic research, etc. Gonzaga version (lecture) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Basic research, etc. Japan version (lecture) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Caracas paper (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Centennial lecture article (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - China lecture (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Creativity - lecture (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Edmonton science conference 11/16/00-11/19/00 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Electron transfer - general principles lecture (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Flory lecture (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Lecture - Guelph: "Basic research in modern society" (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Japan Abstracts - Organometallic Chem.of Pentaammineosmium(II) and Pentammineosmium (III)/Electron Trans. In Chem. Reactions/Mixed Valence molecules (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Lecture: Electron Transfer in Redox Reactions: Historical Perspective. (Dartmouth, Boston College) fall 1986 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Lecture: New Chem. Of Osmium Ammines - an Interface Between Traditional Coordination Chem. and Organometallic Chem. (Dartmouth, Boston College) fall 1986 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Travel and lectures: Bunsentagung - Hamburg, spring 1972 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Travel and lectures: Australian trip, May-June 1973 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Travel and lectures: Santiago, Chile January 1972 XI Congreso Latinoamericano de Quimica (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Travel and lectures: Manchester, England April 1972 Meeting of the Chemical Society (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Travel and lectures through 1973 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Travel and lectures 1974 Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Nitrogen Fixation Symposium Melbourne, Australia, Sept. 1969 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Nuclear Medicine (Detroit) 1980 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Japan trip 1987 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Japan trip 1990 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Japan lecture - Electron Transfer through Macromolecular Systems (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Japan trip 1985 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Oscillating chemical reaction (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Travel and lectures: Poland, summer 1973 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Ottawa - Herzberg lecture (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Oxidation-reduction Book draft (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Primary Research (lecture) (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Royal Society of Chemistry - article (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Royal Society (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Santiago lecture (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Science and Society lecture (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - [no label] (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Travel and lectures: Dublin, Ireland August 1972 Int'l Conference on Coordination Chem. (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Travel and lectures: Nitrogen Fixation Symposium Pullman Washington June 1974 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Anson, Fred - Awards (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Awards - Boxer, Steve (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Awards - Bartlett, N. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Awards - Basolo, Fred (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Bercaw, John E. - Awards (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Awards - Bigeleisen, Jake (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Awards - Bonner, W. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Awards - Bohle, Scott (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Awards - John Brauman (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Awards - Brewer, Leo (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Awards - Gerard L. Closs (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Awards file - James Collman (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Cotton, A1 - awards file (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Awards - Davison, Alan (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Derouane, Eric - Awards (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Deutsch, Edward - Awards (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Awards - Dye, James L. (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Espenson, James - Awards (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Awards - Fayer, Michael (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Ford, Peter - Awards (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Friedman NAS [in pen, label missing] (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Halpern, Jack - Awards (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Murray, Royce - Awards (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Pecora, Robert - Awards (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Gray, Harry B. - Awards (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Awards - Harman, W. Dean (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Awards - Hawthorne, Fred (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Awards - Keith Hodgson (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Awards - Holm, Richard (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Huestus, Wray - Awards (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Awards - Hurst, James (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Hush, Noel (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Hush, Noel - Awards (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Awards - Ibers, J. (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Awards - William Johnson (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Awards - E. King (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Awards - Kubas, Gregory (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Awards - Lagow, Richard (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Lewis, Nathan - Awards file (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Little, William - Awards (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Awards - Margerum, Dale (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Awards - J. T. Meyer (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Awards - McConnell (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Morris, Robert - reprints (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Awards - Michael Pirring (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Awards - Pitzer, Kenneth (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Raymond, Kenneth - awards (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Rowland, Sherwood - awards (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Awards - Luigi Sacconi (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Sargeson, A. - awards (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Solomon, Edward I. - awards (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Sullivan, James - awards (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Awards - Turro, Nicholas (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Norman Sutin - awards (two folders) (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Weaver, Michael J. - awards (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - American Philosophical Society (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Australia - Academy of Science - Journals - National University (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Henry Taube - ACS convention Las Vegas 1982 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - American Chemical Society (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - B Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Basic research (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Bloch, Felix (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Bonner, William (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratories (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Canadian scientists (origin or association) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Catalytica highlights (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Chemistry classes and courses (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - CMR - Center for Materials Research (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Complexes - Equil. and Rates (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Copenhagen Univ. - Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - D Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - C Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - E Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Education (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Emeriti status (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Emerson (Gladys Anderson) Fund (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Equipment - Laboratory inventory (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Executive committee - Chemistry (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - F Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Foundation for Basic Research in Chemistry (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Friedman, Harold (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Full cell mtg. - notes 1985 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - G Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - "General" (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - German exams (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Graduate admissions (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Guggenheim Foundation (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - H Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Haim, Albert - Polemics (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Hercules consulting (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Honor code (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - House Science and Techn. Committee, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Human rights (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Humanities - article Campus Report, 1990 Jun (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Humor (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Hydrogen research folder (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - I Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Impact (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Indian proposal - Argawala Sharma (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Industrial accidents (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Industrial affiliates - General (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Industrial affiliates - Hercules (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Industrial affiliates - ICI America (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Inorganic West Coast lectureship (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - The International Council for Scientific Development (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Inventory - laboratory (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - IUPAC (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - J Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Japanese collaboration (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Japan proposal - Shin Etsu (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Japan - Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Japan proposal #1 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Japanese proposal #2 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Journals - misc. (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Journals - accounts of Chemical Research - J. T. Bunnett, Editor (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Journals - Inorganic chemistry editorial board (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Journals - Acta cientifica venezolana (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Journals - International Journal of Chemical Kinetics (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Journals - Verlag - Inorg. Reactions Zukerman, Oklahoma (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - K Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Keene, F. Richard (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - L Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory safety (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Lab remodeling - Stauffer II (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - LaFollette, Douglas - campaign materials (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Lawrence Berkeley MMRD Chem. Review (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Los Alamos Scientific Laboratory - Personnel security questionnaire (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Lund - correspondence (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence "Mc" (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - M Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Marcus commemorative paper (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Memorandums, Interoffice - Stanford (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Mitsubichi, U.S. (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Mixed valence (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Molecular gymnastics (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - N Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - no label [National Science Foundation?] (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Nuclear arms limitation (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Nuclear disarmament (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - O Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Oakridge National Laboratory (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Osmium chemistry (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - P Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Patent application - Harman and Taube (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Pauling Institute (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Periodic tables (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Dr. Pecora (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Phi Beta Kappa (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Polaroid (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Polyhedron Prize - inorganic (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Bartlett, Neil (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Basolo, Fred (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Bush, Daryle (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Collman, James (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Cotton, F. Albert (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Gray, Harry (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Halpern, Jack (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Hawthorne, M. Frederick (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Marks, Tobin (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Stone, F. G. A. (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Wilkinson, Geoffrey (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Postdoctoral inquiries (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Referring - manuscripts (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - R Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Refereening - proposals (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Refereeing - theses (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Research letters - former students (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Rubenstein, Edward (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - S Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Henry Taube - sabbatical leave plans 1968 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Sacramento State Capitol 1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Safety (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - San Jose State (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Saskatchewan, University (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Henry Taube - University of Saskatchewan Alumni Association, May 1984 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Seminar committee (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Seminars - Inorganic (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Schaefer, William (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - School (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Leo Sides Travel Agency (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Sigma Xi, Society of the (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Sloan Foundation, The: Nominations, reports, rosters (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Soinks, J. T. W. (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Stanford Research Institute (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Stanford Retirement Program (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Stauffer renovation (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Stone, F. G. A. (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Stoughton, R. W. (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Student advisees (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Student forms (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Student papers (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - SSRL Synchronotron Radiation Proposal (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Swedish Science Research Council - October 1984 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Tsuchida, Eishun (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Telephone (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Thomas Research Corporation (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Trip file 1996 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - U Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Undergraduate major curriculum in chemistry (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - United Airlines (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - UC/Berkeley - department review (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - California, University of (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - University of Michigan - evaluation of chemistry department (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Government Office of Science and Technology (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - University of Michigan - evaluation of chemistry department (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - University of Southern California - evaluation of graduate program in chemistry (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - V Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - W Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Vanadium chemistry - research (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Woodside Priory Foundation (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Wilmarth, Wayne (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - XYZ Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Publication list (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Reprints 1995-2003 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - 1990-1992 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Reprints 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Reprints 1985-1987 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Reprints 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Reprints 1982 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Reprints 1981 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Reprints 1980 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Reprints 1979 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Reprints 1978 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Reprints 1977 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Reprints 1976 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Reprints 1975 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Reprints 1974 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Reprints 1973 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Reprints 1972 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Reprints 1971 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Reprints 1970 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Reprints 1969 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Reprints 1968 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Reprints 1967 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Reprints 1966 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Reprints 1965 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Reprints 1964 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Reprints 1963 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Reprints 1962 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Reprints 1961 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Reprints 1960 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Reprints 1959 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Reprints 1958 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Reprints 1957 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Reprints 1956 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Reprints 1955 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Reprints 1954 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Reprints 1953 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Reprints 1952 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Reprints 1951 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Reprints prior to 1950 (Box 20, Folder 40)
- Papers, Accession ARCH.2008-375
  - Cards and Awards (Box 1)
  - Dr. Gerhard Herzberg and the University of Saskatchewan, 1994; 2.1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Three Generations of Saskatchewan Chemists Part 2: Dr. William A.G. Graham, 1995; 2.2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Three Generations of Saskatchewan Chemists Part 3: Dr. Alaa Abd El Aziz, 1995; 2.3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Unlabeled reel (Box 2)